If you have any questions, don't hesitate to contact us. 
 
Best regards

Mario Zelasny
Diploma in Economics
Diploma in Building Engineering
TÜV-chartered Surveyor of real estate valuation
and equivalent titles similar land rights



Wagemann + Partner GbR 
Steuerberater | Wirtschaftsprüfer | CPA 
Eisenzahnstraße 64 
10709 Berlin

fon: +49 (30) 890 617 91
fax: +49 (30) 893 889 99 
email: m.zelasny@wagemann.de
homepage: www.wagemann.net

Wagemann + Partner is a member of Integra International. 
homepage: www.integra-international.net
Global association of independent auditors, business and tax consultants.
Weitere Informationen / for further information: www.wagemann.net/unternehmen/international.html


Please note that e-mail communication via internet is not secure, as unauthorized third parties might be able to have access to your data. To avoid unauthorized knowledge and falsification of your data during e-mail transfer please arrange an encoding procedure with us.

The information contained in this email is intended solely for the addressee. Access to this email by anyone else is unauthorized. If you are not the intended recipient, any form of disclosure, reproduction, distribution or any action taken or refrained from in reliance on it, is prohibited and may be unlawful. Please notify the sender immediately. All statements of opinion or advice directed via this email to our clients are subject to the terms and conditions expressed in the governing Wagemann & Partner client engagement letter. The content of this email is not legally binding unless confirmed by letter. The sending of emails to us will not constitute compliance with any time limits or deadlines.Ende der Nachricht. End of the message.

