If you have any questions, don't hesitate to contact us. 
 
Best regards

Christian Täge
Real Estate Assessor



W+P Real Estate GmbH
Paulsborner Straße 3
10709 Berlin

fon: +49 (30) 890 617 91 
fax: +49 (30) 893 889 219 
email: c.taege@wp-real-estate.de

CEO: Mario Zelasny

register court: Amtsgerichts Charlottenburg 
register number: HRB 125 913 B
VAT ID: DE 272 236 580


Please note that e-mail communication via internet is not secure, as unauthorized third parties might be able to have access to your data. To avoid unauthorized knowledge and falsification of your data during e-mail transfer please arrange an encoding procedure with us.

The information contained in this email is intended solely for the addressee. Access to this email by anyone else is unauthorized. If you are not the intended recipient, any form of disclosure, reproduction, distribution or any action taken or refrained from in reliance on it, is prohibited and may be unlawful. Please notify the sender immediately. All statements of opinion or advice directed via this email to our clients are subject to the terms and conditions expressed in the governing Wagemann & Partner client engagement letter. The content of this email is not legally binding unless confirmed by letter. The sending of emails to us will not constitute compliance with any time limits or deadlines.Ende der Nachricht. End of the message.

